Are you in charge of the funeral parlor?
Not really.
I'm just an embalmer.
Tell me then.
How much would you charge
to cremate one leg?
That is
a unique question.
You haven't been around much then.
I don't pride myself on such things.
But if you want
to hear a practical answer,
you should be sincere as well.
At least tell me
some specific information.
I avoided the funeral parlor in this area
because I didn't want my family to know.
It would be troublesome.
So don't ask me so many questions.
Just tell me.
Does it cost more to cremate one leg
or an entire body?
I'll compare the prices.
Sorry,
but are you going
to undergo an amputation?
Yes. Bone cancer.
I either cut it off or die.
Your mental state seems stable.
Everyone says so.
They say I'm still young
and well financially.
As long as I can stay alive,
losing a leg won't impact me too much.
They're not right.
It will definitely impact you.
I know a young lady who had an amputation.
It took her a few years
to get her life back on track.
Even so, she's doing very well now.
She has a successful career
and is lively and energetic.
Losing a leg hasn't affected
her optimism or pleasant nature.
That has nothing to do with me.
Just tell me the price.
You've been talking
about money since just now.
Maybe money is very important to you,
but forgive me for being frank.
I don't think
money can determine someone's value.
I'm already at this stage of my life.
There's no point
in saying those empty words.
I know it all too well.
There's no point in asking you.
I've thought it through.
If all else fails,
I'll find an empty bridge
and jump off it to end everything.
I will no longer cause anyone trouble.
You're wrong again.
If you really want to jump off a bridge,
you would be causing trouble
for public service workers.
The bridge you choose is also important.
Take my hometown's Nanping Bridge
as an example.
If a body is washed upstream,
Ningfu Town would have to deal with it.
If it is washed downstream,
Ji'an Town would need to deal with it.
If it happens to be midstream,
both towns would have to meet
and argue about it.
That would be very troublesome.
You're pretty amusing.
Very few people say that about me.
I know you're having a tough time.
I can't say I understand how you feel.
But I want to tell you
that everyone has times
when they're tired of life.
The reasons may vary,
but the pain is the same.
Including you?
Including me.
You're kidding me.
You look perfectly fine.
In the face of death,
everyone is the same.
Some family members
want to use special coffins, unique urns,
or expensive headstones
to prove the deceased was special.
However, these are all just illusions.
When it comes to death,
everyone is the same.
We can only prove how special we are
by living well.
Just like the disabled lady
that I mentioned.
Do you like this lady?
ADAPTED FROM THE ORIGINAL WORK
"LOVER" BY SHE MU SI
In the next decade, import substitution
will be the priority
of China's medical device industry.
Currently, the problem we face
is the lack of synergy
between the upstream and downstream
of our supply chain.
So we need to come together
to build a single team
of medicine, supplies,
and engineering services
that can complement each other.
All right, take a rest.
I've been listening to that
for the past two days.
What are you doing?
Has the United Nations
invited you to deliver a speech?
To me, this opportunity is as important
as a United Nations speech.
Do you remember when I mentioned
my former boss, Ms. Huang?
She's interested in the business plan
that Wang Xixia and I created.
She will invest a lot of money
to help us take off.
Have you discussed this with Maidong?
We can't talk about this over the phone.
When he returns and his mood is better,
I'll tell him everything honestly.
Why are you staring at me?
A mother knows her daughter.
Tell him honestly?
Do you want to keep this from him?
How can I hide this from him?
But I have to find a way
to talk to him about this.
Who was the one bragging to me?
If we like each other,
we should be together and enjoy dating.
I'll still return to Shanghai after--
All right! I know I did say that.
But can you stop teasing me?
Did I do that?
Seriously.
I'm thrilled to see
both of you getting serious
in your relationship.
The more serious it is,
the more difficult it gets.
We're in our honeymoon phase
and we have to be long-distance.
I think he might not
be willing to do that.
Is it just up to him?
Is he going to break up with me?
The two of you aren't married yet.
You can't force him.
I won't let him go.
At worst, I'll find some allies
to help me secretly.
Good luck.
The last time that Maidong had pink eye
was when his parents divorced.
He didn't tell me about that.
Just pretend you don't know.
He must have cried a lot recently.
We're here to see flowers.
Let's not talk about this.
Have you read this poem?
"Pick the flowers while they are blooming
Soon nothing will be left
Save bare boughs and tears"
You don't get to witness spring
in our town every year.
Take a look and treasure it.
Mrs. Chen,
I know what you're trying to say.
You're so smart.
I won't say more.
Otherwise,
you youngsters get fed up with it.
What do you mean?
You're so smart and adorable.
How could I get fed up with you?
If not for you,
Chen Maidong and I
wouldn't even be together.
But Mrs. Chen,
I also want you
to understand the situation I'm in.
I can't give up on my life in Shanghai.
I have a career and friends there.
Of course.
Times have changed.
It's understandable for women
to build a career.
I knew you were the most understanding.
Thank you so much for saying that.
But Mrs. Chen, don't worry.
I will be good to Chen Maidong.
Although I haven't thought
of a perfect plan,
I believe that I will.
I believe you.
But you have to tell me the truth.
Are you and Maidong just dating casually
or have you considered marriage?
Previously, I didn't
put much thought into it.
I felt that if we like each other,
we should be together.
We can be friends even if we break up.
But Mrs. Chen,
I'm now very sure
that I need him to be in my life.
I'm very thankful
to hear you say that.
Well, Jie,
I want to tell you this
from the bottom of my heart.
I think once you meet the right person,
you should get married.
I'm not old-fashioned
and I'm not urging you to have children.
I just think
if a man and a woman
just want to have fun,
they may hang out or move in together.
It does make things easier.
When they split up,
it saves a lot of trouble.
But such a relationship
that leaves no trace
won't help one to grow.
Although maintaining a marriage
or having a divorce
comes with a huge price
and will even leave behind
some unhappy experiences,
this in itself is meaningful.
In one's life,
one should earnestly get hurt
and suffer losses.
That way, you get
to live a fulfilling life.
When I was young,
I often got into conflicts with others
because of my poor temperament.
In the past,
I hoped I could forget it all.
But after Ms. Lin's passing,
I've been living vicariously
through memories.
Not only do I miss her,
but I also think of all the friends
who have hurt me or been hurt by me.
Jie,
life is full of ups and downs.
Mrs. Chen,
you're the best.
I knew you would be my ally.
No matter when,
girls help girls.
Girl…
What? Girl what?
"Girls" means us.
"Girls."
Great.
Girls are great!
Yes!
Great!
Good.
Didn't I tell you so?
Nothing is good or bad.
But everything should be in moderation.
Looking at your tongue,
your liver and stomach are quite balanced.
Drink less high-proof alcohol
and you will be fine.
Stick out your tongue.
Let me take another look.
Mom.
Why are you getting a consultation?
Dr. Cui's fee is very high.
No. What are you saying?
I came to Nanping
to volunteer at a free clinic anyway.
He has been waiting all morning for you!
If I didn't do this,
I wouldn't know what to say to him.
Dr. Cui, go inside to chat.
I'll cut some fruit for you.
-Thank you.
-Not at all. Please go inside.
-Please, sit.
-Thank you.
-Not at all.
Cui Ge, you came all of a sudden,
and Xixia didn't even tell me.
I didn't tell Xixia.
Is this not a good time?
Not at all.
That's not what I mean.
Don't worry.
Your mother is very healthy.
If I didn't give her a checkup,
we would have nothing to talk about.
Well, Cui Ge, is there something you need?
XI
Wait.
Do you want me
to help you with a proposal?
I want you to take a look at this
and tell me if Xixia will like it.
XI
"Xi."
Well, I…
I dare not make such a decision
on her behalf.
If it's clothes or shoes,
I might be able to help.
But for a ring, you should ask her.
Actually, I've asked her indirectly
about her preferences
before I got this.
Then…
That's great.
Then you don't have to check with me.
But I'm not sure
if she wants to get married.
Xixia probably began fantasizing
about her wedding
when she was six.
Talking about it is one thing,
but actually getting married is another.
I've been wondering
why independent women like the two of you
would need to get married.
Men take up space and are troublesome.
Besides,
this would be my second marriage.
What makes me indispensable?
What can I give her?
Cui Ge, not many men share your thoughts.
Precisely because Xixia and I
are modern women,
we are used to being misunderstood.
In fact, we aren't against marriage
or think that a DINK lifestyle
is necessary.
The key is meeting the right person
at the right time.
Since we have already turned 30,
we should live the lives we want
and be responsible for our decisions.
So don't worry
about marriage or kids for us.
I understand.
Thank you.
Zhuang Jie,
don't worry.
I'll treat Xixia well.
I know.
I MISS YOU
Are you crazy?
I was napping and didn't check my phone.
I miss you too.
See you tomorrow.
Are your eyes feeling better?
Much better.
That's dirty.
I went to the pharmacy
to get you some eye drops.
Just to be safe.
No need. I'll do it myself tonight.
I'll do it for you.
Let's head back first.
Open your eyes.
Come on.
Stay still. We'll do this quickly.
You lost so much weight.
I should have been by your side.
It's fine.
You didn't come
straight to see me after coming back.
Didn't you miss me?
Get on.
I'll buy you breakfast.
Okay.
Come to the apartment tonight?
Cui Ge.
I want to ask you something too.
Would you accept
a long-distance relationship?
Honestly?
Of course.
If we were married,
then there would be no choice
but to overcome it.
But if I still had a choice,
I wouldn't want to.
Why?
Because
I'm no longer a young lad.
I'm very aware that time and distance
will surely take a toll on a relationship.
I wouldn't want to take the risk.
Let's be realistic.
What I need is someone who eats with me
and sleeps by my side
rather than communicating
through chat or phone calls.
Anyway, to a mature man,
it doesn't mean much.
Today,
Health and Healing Channel
will narrate a prose
written by Mr. Wang Zengqi.
When people mention him,
they always call him
China's last pure literary scholar.
He once came up with a famous quote.
It goes,
"Love is non-professional.
It has nothing to do
with one's talent or capability.
It grows like flowers and trees,
like our love and attachment
to time and seasons."
So,
when we find frustrations
and contradictions in life…
Contradictory.
"Among the people of Chu,
a man sold shields and lances.
He praised them and said,
'My shields are so firm,
there is nothing that can pierce them.'
He also said…"
If you keep playing with your toes,
someone will come to beat you up.
You still haven't memorized a single word.
What if Yan tests you?
Jie, just worry about yourself.
Leave me be.
Listening to this makes me depressed.
Are you depressed?
We're more depressed than you.
Do you want to repeat a year?
To me, this fable is a piece of cake.
Keep on bragging. Recite one for me.
Why should I?
One word sums it up. "Contradictory."
Forget about the people of Chu.
Just look at you.
In what way am I contradictory?
Last night, you were on the phone
with someone in Shanghai for two hours.
Then you had a video call
with Xixia for half an hour.
You said,
"I don't know how to tell Maidong."
In the morning,
you asked Yan to help you
look up tickets to Shanghai.
Now you're putting on makeup
to go on a date with Maidong.
Aren't you being contradictory?
Your grades are so horrible,
but you have time to spy on me.
I've also learned this idiom,
"Flying off the handle."
Jie, you'll find peace in honesty.
It's never too late to change!
Chen Maidong,
I won't break up with you.
I'm going back to Shanghai…
I can't say that.
Chen Maidong, I…
I didn't tell you
because you've been down,
so I didn't dare…
What am I talking about?
Why am I saying this right off the bat?
Chen Maidong,
it's different this time.
It's a different…
How long are you going
to linger down there?
Should I take a nap?
What?
Are we having a meeting?
Let's have a serious chat.
Behave for a while!
Have some self-control.
It's a bit late
to say that.
Here.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Then is there anything you want to say?
I don't know where to start.
Chen Maidong,
I can be your best friend.
You already are.
Then tell me
what I can do
to make you feel better.
Actually,
Ms. Lin left the world peacefully.
I also know
that death
might have been a good thing for her.
I comfort others every day,
so I understand that.
To me,
there are two kinds of goodbyes.
Parting in life and parting by death.
The last thing Ms. Lin said to me
was for me to live a good life with you.
And the last thing I said to her was,
"Ms. Lin,
I'm going to tidy up the things.
I'll come back later to listen to you."
But when I turned around,
she was already gone.
I once thought
that the most difficult thing in the world
to get over was death.
So when you told me
I am a noble person,
I neither agreed
nor denied it.
But when a separation
turned into eternal loss
in a matter of minutes,
I suddenly realized
that a parting in life
might be even scarier.
So Zhuang Jie,
I don't want to act tough anymore.
Now,
I don't want you
to disappear from my life in any manner.
Chen Maidong,
me too.
I won't allow you to disappear
from my life in any manner.
Do you know?
When I was in Shanghai,
I met many outstanding men
who were successful in every aspect.
They all knew
how to be flawless in conduct,
how to be gentlemanly, caring,
amusing, and witty.
But I was never attracted to them.
I used to think
there was something wrong with me
because I couldn't find a boyfriend.
It was not until your reappearance
that I realized
I wasn't interested
in the lions and tigers in the zoo.
I only have eyes for a lone wolf like you.
You never need to pretend
to be strong with me.
Although
I have not experienced
as much death as you,
I know how hard it is
to overcome the parting in life
that you described.
You're already doing a great job.
In the future,
you don't have to be so great.
I'll be right by your side.
Get some sleep.
Do you like this lady?
More than that.
I love her.
As long as I think of her,
no matter how difficult things are,
I'll have some hope.
She's pretty lucky.
I'm the lucky one.
What I want to say is,
whether or not you have this leg,
you are the hope
of your family and loved ones.
Don't leave them so easily
or decide for yourself how they feel.
The harder it is,
the more you must try.
Do your best
to live out the rest of your life
with your loved ones.
Grandma?
ALL ANIMALS IN THIS PROGRAM
WERE TREATED KINDLY